[{"order":"1","question":"Molly","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Molly is a <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MDMA\">type of Ectasy</a>.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MDMA"},{"order":"2","question":"Alice","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Alice is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alice_(programming_language)\">a programming language.</a>","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alice_(programming_language)"},{"order":"3","question":"PHP","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"PHP is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Php\">a popular Web programming language</a>, not to be confused with PCP, a hallucinogenic drug.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Php"},{"order":"4","question":"Robo","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Robo is <a href=\"http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=robo\">slang for dextromethorphan</a>, a hallucinogen that is the active ingredient of many cough suppressants, including Robitussin.","url":"http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=robo"},{"order":"5","question":"Bliss","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"BLISS is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BLISS_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a>, although it's also a <a href=\"http://tardis.wikia.com/wiki/Bliss_(drug)\">fictional drug</a> in Dr. Who.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BLISS_(programming_language)"},{"order":"6","question":"Pane","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Pane is <a href=\"http://www.noslang.com/drugs/dictionary/p/\">a slang for LSD</a>.","url":"http://www.noslang.com/drugs/dictionary/p/"},{"order":"7","question":"Elixir","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Elixir is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elixir_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> released in 2012.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elixir_(programming_language)"},{"order":"8","question":"DXM","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"DXM is short for <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dextromethorphan\">Dextromethorphan</a>, a cough suppressant that is used recreationally as a hallucinogen.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dextromethorphan"},{"order":"9","question":"Little b","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Little b is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_b\">a programming language</a> designed for biological research.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_b"},{"order":"10","question":"Brainfuck","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Brainfuck is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brainfuck_(programming_language)\">an \"esoteric programming language,\"</a> a language designed for amusement or theoretical interest but of little practical use.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brainfuck_(programming_language)"},{"order":"11","question":"MDMA","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"MDMA is the chemical name for <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MDMA\">ecstasy</a>.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MDMA"},{"order":"12","question":"Microdot","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Microdot is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lysergic_acid_diethylamide\">slang</a> for a small tablet of LSD.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lysergic_acid_diethylamide"},{"order":"13","question":"Bigwig","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Bigwig is <a herf=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bigwig_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> for Web applications.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bigwig_(programming_language)"},{"order":"14","question":"Magik","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Magik is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magik_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> invented in 1989.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magik_(programming_language)"},{"order":"15","question":"Emsel","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Emsel is <a href=\"http://www.noslang.com/drugs/dictionary/e/\">slang</a> for morphine.","url":"http://www.noslang.com/drugs/dictionary/e/"},{"order":"16","question":"Triple C","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Triple C is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coricidin#Recreational_use\">slang</a> for Coricidin Cough & Cold, which is used recreationally in high doses to induce a trippy feeling.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coricidin#Recreational_use"},{"order":"17","question":"Groovy","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Groovy is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Groovy_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> invented in 2003.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Groovy_(programming_language)"},{"order":"18","question":"Ruby on Rails","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Ruby on Rails is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruby_on_rails\">a popular Web application framework</a>.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruby_on_rails"},{"order":"19","question":"Scala","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Scala is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scala_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> invented in 2003.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scala_(programming_language)"},{"order":"20","question":"Mesc","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1","feedback":"Mesc, short for \"Mescaline,\" is the active ingredient in <a href=\"http://www.getsmartaboutdrugs.com/drugs/peyote_and_mescaline.html?vOverview\">peyote</a>, a cactus that causes hallucinations.","url":"http://www.getsmartaboutdrugs.com/drugs/peyote_and_mescaline.html?vOverview"},{"order":"21","question":"Adenine","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Adenine is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adenine_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> named after a component of DNA.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adenine_(programming_language)"},{"order":"22","question":"Whitespace","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Whitespace is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whitespace_(programming_language)\">an esoteric programming language</a> that depends entirely on \"whitespace\" characters, such as spaces and tabs.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whitespace_(programming_language)"},{"order":"23","question":"Oxygene","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Oxygene is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oxygene_(programming_language)\">a programming language</a> released in 2011.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oxygene_(programming_language)"},{"order":"24","question":"Grass","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"1,2","feedback":"This one's a freebie. Grass is a slang for marijuana. GRASS is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GRASS_(programming_language)\">an old programming language</a> for 2D animations.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GRASS_(programming_language)"},{"order":"25","question":"Euphoria","choice1":"Drug","choice2":"Code","correct":"2","feedback":"Euphoria is <a href=\"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Euphoria_(programming_language)#History\">a programming language</a> invented in 1993.","url":"http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Euphoria_(programming_language)#History"}]
